David Attenborough: A Life on Our Planet is a documentary,
drama film directed by Alastair Fothergill.
The story of life on our planet by the man who has seen
more of the natural world than any other.
In more than 90 years, Attenborough has visited every continent on the globe, exploring the wild
places of our planet and documenting the living world in all its variety and wonder.
Addressing the biggest challenges facing life on our planet, the film
offers a powerful message of hope for future generations.
Self, played by David Attenborough.
Young David, played by Max Hughes.
David Attenborough: A Life on Our Planet is a 2020 British documentary film narrated
by David Attenborough and produced and directed by Jonnie Hughes.
The film acts as a "witness statement", through which Attenborough shares first-hand his concern for the
current state of the planet due to humanity's impact on nature and his hopes for the future.
It was released on Netflix on 4 October 2020, along with
a companion book A Life on Our Planet.
The film explores themes of climate change, biography,
destruction of planet, nature, evolution.
The tone is emotional.